Guide to the Time Inc. Annex Files 1854, 1909, 1923-2014 MS 3009-RG 39
New-York Historical Society
- Public Affairs: International: 1958: International Seminars (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: International: 1958: Japanese Advertising Study Group's Visit to U.S., 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: International: 1958: Photo Exhibit, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: International: 1960: Comité International: de l'Organisation Scientifique (CIOS), 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs: International: 1962: Life Illuminations in Japan, 1960, undated (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: International: 1962: Asian Golf Tour (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: International: 1964: Japanese Economic Mission (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs: Journalism Advertisement Campaign, 1940 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1936: National Automobile Show (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 19)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1938-1939: Houses (Offsite-box 3948, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1938-1939: Houses (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Miscellaneous, 1957, 1965, 1968-1969, 1977 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 7-8)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1939: Michigan Life: Conference, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 2-3)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1939: Yale Life: Conference (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1939 and Later: Exhibits, 1946-1951, undated (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1940: Exhibits: Cranbrook (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Life: Exhibition Cranbrook, 1940 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1940: Houses, 1938-1940 (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 7)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1941: and Later Houses, Miscellaneous, 1944-1947 (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1942: Art Competition for Men in the Armed-Forces, 1942-1943, 1977, undated (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1944: "Know Our United Nations", 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 10)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1944: World War II Patience Posters (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1944: World War II Patience Posters, undated (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1947: Christmas Show Grand Central Station (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1947: New America, 1946-1949 (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 13-14)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1951: Photography, 1937-1938, 1951 (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 15-16)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1952: National Golf Day, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1954: Action (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1954: National Golf Day, 1953-1954 (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1954: National Golf Day, 1952-55, undated (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1954: Olympic Team Fund (Offsite-box 3949, Folder 19)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1954: Olympic Team Fund [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R83)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1954: Photography, 1954-1956, undated (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1955: National Golf Day, 1954-1955 (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1955: Olympic Team Fund, 1955-1960 (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 3-4)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1955-1957: National Gold Days Medals, 1952-1954 (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 5-6)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1956 and Later: Illumination, 1956-1960, 1969 (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 7-8)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1957: People-to-People (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1958: Arden House Conference, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 10)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1958: Marketing Round Tables, 1958-1959 (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: American Veterans (AMVETS) (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Blurbs (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Cartoons, undated (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Discussion Guides, etc. (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Junior Chamber of Commerce (Jaycees), 1960-1961 (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: National Recreation Association, 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Progress Reports (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 18-19)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Pictures, undated (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Promotion (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 21)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Publicity (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 22-23)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3950, Folder 24)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1960-1962: National Purpose: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1961: Opera, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1963 and Later: Educations Grants, 1963-1965 (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1964: America's Cup Races (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1964: "The World We Live In" Symposium (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1964: Space Tour, 1963-1965, 1978, undated (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 6-9)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1965: Space Tour (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 10)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1966: Space Tour, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 11-13)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1967: America's Cup Races, 1967, undated (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1968: Caltech "The Far Reach of Science", 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1969: Space Tour (Offsite-box 3951, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1969: Space Tour (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1970: Photography Contest, undated (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1971: Luncheon: Secretary of Treasury John B. Connally (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1979: "Life: "The First Decade" (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1982: National Air and Space Museum" 25 Years of Space Exploration, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1982: Smithsonian's National Museum of National History, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1983: Eisenstaedt Brooklyn Bridge Centennial, 1981-1985, undated (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 7)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1987: Gordon Parks Retrospective at New York Public Library, 1982-1987 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1991: Gone with the Wind Luncheon with Alexandra Ripley held 9/21 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Life: 1992/3: Exhibit: Somalia's Cry, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 10)
  25 photo-slides; Label on each: "Somalia's Cry Photo Perspectives December 7-26 1993 Equitable Building North Gallery 7th Ave 52nd St. NYC"
- Public Affairs: Life, 1998-2002 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: Life: Contracts: All Contracts Except Dallas Cinema Associates (DCA) [RESTRICTED], 1967-1968, 1989 (Offsite-box R83)
- Public Affairs: Life: Contracts: All Dallas Cinema Associates (DCA) [RESTRICTED], 1967-1968, 1978 (Offsite-box R83)
- Public Affairs: Life: Relaunch: 1978 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1979 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1980 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1981 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1982 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1983 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1984 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: January-June 1985 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 19)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: July-December 1985 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1/86-6/86, 1986 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 21)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 7/86-12/86, 1986 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 22)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: January 1987 – July 1987 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 23)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1987 (August-December) (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 24)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1988, 1987 (Offsite-box 3952, Folder 25)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1988 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Life: Release: 1989 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 2-3)
- Public Affairs: Life: Releases: 1990 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Life: Space Tours 1964-66, 1964-1966 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Life: Miscellaneous, 1955-1961, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Life: Camps Literature, 1943-1948 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 6-8)
- Public Affairs: Life: Camps Mailings, 1937-1955 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 9-10)
- Public Affairs: Life: Camps Publicity, 1937-1947, 1982, undated (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: Life: Camps Miscellaneous, 1937-1964 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 12-13)
- Public Affairs: Life: Spanish: 1960-1962 Literary Contest (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Money: 1996 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs: Money: 1997 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: Money: Miscellaneous, 1993-1997 (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: National Golf Day 1953 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 10)
- Public Affairs: National Golf Day 1954 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: National Golf Day 1955 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: National Golf Day 1952 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Olympic Team Fund 1954 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: People: 1989: Diana, Princess of Wales Gala, Winter Garden :New York Financial Center (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs: People: 1989: Diana, Princess of Wales Chicago Visit: Press Coverage (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 19)
- Public Affairs: People: 1989: Diana, Princess of Wales Chicago Visit: Gala, Field Museum (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs: People: 1989: Diana, Princess of Wales Chicago Visit: Luncheon, Drake Hotel (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 21)
- Public Affairs: People: 1989: Diana, Princess of Wales Chicago Visit: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3953, Folder 22)
- Public Affairs: People: Miscellaneous, 1985-1997 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Sports Illustrated: 1956-1957: Hungarian Athletes Freedom Tour, 1956-1958 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 2-3)
- Public Affairs: Sports Illustrated: 1956-57: Hungarian Athletes Freedom Tour, 1956-1957 (Offsite-box 4035, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Sports Illustrated: Exhibits: Art Show: 1955 and 1956, 1955-1956 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 4-5)
- Public Affairs: Sports Illustrated: Exhibits: Art Show: 1962 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Sports Illustrated: Exhibits: Art Show: 1965 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 7)
- Public Affairs: Sports Illustrated: Exhibits: Art Show: 1969 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Sports Illustrated: Miscellaneous, 1962, 1984, 1993-1994, undated (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Sports Illustrated For Kids: Miscellaneous, 1988-1993 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 10)
- Public Affairs: Temple-Eastex: 1972: "Big Thicket", 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: Temple-Eastex: Sandyland Surcharge, 1977 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1940: Time Foundation, 1937-1940 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1953: "100 Young Men" (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1959: "Form Givers at Mid-Century", 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1964: Seminar "The Environment of Change" (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1965: Asia Newstour, 1964-1969 (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 17-19)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1965: Thanat Khoman Visit (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1966: College Presidents Meeting November 12-14, Airlie House (Offsite-box 3954, Folder 21)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1966: Time for Adventure, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1967: College Student Seminar (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1967: National Collegiate Presidential Primary (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1968: Choice '68, 1967-1968, undated (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1969: Newstour of Far East, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1969: Newstour of Far East Briefing: Time: Newstour of Far East: February 1969 (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1969: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 7)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1969-71: Housing Industry Presidents Conference, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1970-80: Miscellaneous, 1970-1971, undated (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1971: Newstour "Report on America" (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 10-11)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1971: Newstour "Report on America": Background, undated (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1971: Newstour "Report on America": Summary, undated (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1971: Superjet Conference 6/4-5/71 (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1971: World Trade Symposium (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1971-1972: China News Tour (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1973: European Conference (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1973: Housing Industry Conference (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1973: Japan/USA Survey, 1973, undated (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 19)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1973 April 5-7, Newstour Reunion Agenda and Meeting Places, 1972-1973, undated (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1975 Newstour of Mideast, 1974-1975 (Offsite-box 3955, Folder 21-23)
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in tape. Label on container: "TIME: Magazine Middle East News Tour January 17-31, 1975, Ralph P. Davidson, Publisher, TIME: host"
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in tape. Label on container: "February 6, 1975 Auditorium Mr. G. = briefing of Middle East Tour Intro by A. Huskell"
- Public Affairs: Time: Briefing: Time: Newstour of Far East: February 1969 Binder (empty) (Offsite-box 3956, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Time: Report on America 1971: Background Binder (empty) (Offsite-box 3956, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs: Time: Report on America 1971: Summary Binder (empty) (Offsite-box 3956, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Time: Africa/Mideast Newstour 1978: Notes and Reports: Africa Binder (empty) (Offsite-box 3956, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Time: Newstour 1981 Binder (empty) (Offsite-box 3956, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Time: Newstour '81 Notes and Reports, 1981 (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Time: Newstour 1985: Advance Reading Material Binder (empty) (Offsite-box 3956, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Time: Newstour 1985: Backgrounders Binder (empty) (Offsite-box 3956, Folder 7)
- Public Affairs: Time: Newstour 1985: Notes and Reports Binder (empty) (Offsite-box 3956, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Time Newstours, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1975: Symposium "The Atlantic Alliance" (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 1-2)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Leadership Conference: Political Swings (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Leadership Conference: Task Force I (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 4-5)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Leadership Conference: Task Force II (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Leadership Conference: Task Force III (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Leadership Conference: Task Force IV (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Leadership Conference: Task Force V (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 10-11)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Leadership Conference: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 12-13)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Leadership Mini-Conference (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1976: Mini-Leadership Meetings (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 15)
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in tape. Label on container: "Mini Leadership Meeting 4/12/76 reels #1"
  1 audiotape reel: analog, 7 in., 1/4 in tape. Label on container: "Mini Leadership Meeting 4/12/76 reels #2"
- Public Affairs: Time: 1977: October 16-19 Time Update on America '77 Newstour (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1977: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3957, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1978: Africa/Mideast Newstour: Background and Research Box (Offsite-box 3958, Object 1)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1978: Africa/Mid East Newstour: Notes and Reports (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1978: Africa/Mid East Newstour: Participants, undated (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1978: Mideast News-Tour (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 3)
  1 film reel: 8mm. On label: "News Tour '78 Donald N. Frey"
- Public Affairs: Time: 1978: National Portrait Gallery Donation of Original Time: Cover Portraits, 1977-1978, undated (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1978: National Portrait Gallery Donation of Original Time Cover Portraits [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R83)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1978: Proposed News Tour; Panama, Venezuela, Brazil and Cuba, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1978: Miscellaneous, 1978, 1984, 1992, undated (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1979: Middle East Conference (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 7)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1980: Seminar on Military Manpower (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1981: Newstour, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1981: Newstour Participants, undated (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 10)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1981-1983: Miscellaneous (empty) (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1981 (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1983: Newstour '83 Participants and Schedule (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1983: Newstour '83 Transcripts (1) (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 14-15)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1983: Newstour '83 Transcripts (2) (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 16-17)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1983: Newstour '83 Transcripts (3) (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1984: Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 19)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1985 Newstour Pacific Rim Advance Reading Materials (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 20-21)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1985: Newstour Pacific Rim Backgroudner (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 22-23)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1985: Newstour Pacific Rim Notes and Reports (Offsite-box 3959, Folder 24)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1985: Newstour Pacific Rim Notes and Reports (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 1)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1985: Southeast Asia Newstour, 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 2)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1985: Miscellaneous, 1985-1990, undated (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1986: Miscellaneous, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1988: Environment Conference Boulder, Colorado, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 5-8)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1988: Environment Conference Binder, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1990, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 10)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1990: Newstour (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 11)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1990: Newstour 1990 Eastern Europe (empty) (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1993- (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 13)
- Public Affairs: Time: 1995: Newstour India (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 14)
- Public Affairs: Time: Time 100, 1999 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 15)
- Public Affairs: Time: Exhibits: Music, 1945-1948 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 16)
- Public Affairs: Time: Miscellaneous, 1987-1990, 1996 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1933: World's Fair Chicago, 1933-1934, 1965-1966, undated (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 18)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1936: National Automobile Show (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 19)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1937: Automobile Show (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 20)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1939: Subscriber's Library (World's Fair), 1939, 1952 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 21-22)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1939: World's Fair New York, 1937-1938 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 23)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1939-47: Bureau of Special Services, 1940-1945, undated (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 24)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1940-1941: Council for Democracy (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 25)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1940-51: American Red Cross, 1940-1951 (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 26)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1941: United China Relief (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 27)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1941: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3960, Folder 28)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1941-1943: Club Bureau, 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 1-2)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1943: Syracuse Project (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 3)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Air Objective Folders (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Air Objective [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R84)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Air Objectives Folders (Sample), 1944 (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 4)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: America (Russian), 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: America (South American) (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: America Magazine: South America [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R84)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: America Magazine South America, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 5)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Atlas, 1944 (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 7)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Buaer Newsletter, 1941-1945 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 6)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Carrier War: Copies (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 7-8)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Carrier War: Miscellaneous, 1944-1945 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: "Carrier War": Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1941-1945 (Offsite-box R84)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Combat Morale German and Japanese Soldier, 1942-1944 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 10-11)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Commence Shooting: Navy Photograph Manual (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 12)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Commence Shooting: Navy Photograph Manual [RESTRICTED] (Offsite-box R84)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: "Commence Shooting" (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 8)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: En Guardia, 1941 (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 9)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Field Manual "Physical Training", 1943 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 13-14)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: "Get That Fighter", 1943-1944 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 15-16)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Get That Fighter [RESTRICTED], 1944 (Offsite-box R84)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: "How to Shoot the U.S. Army Rifle", 1942-1943 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 17-18)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: "Japan and the Japanese", 1944 (Offsite-box 3961, Folder 19-20)
- Public Affairs: Time Inc.: 1942-1945: War Task: Libertaçâo, 1944 (Offsite-box 4036, Folder 10)